Column Name	Description
country	Name of the country
child_mort	Death of children under 5 years of age per 1000 live births
exports	Exports of goods and services per capita. Given as %age of the GDP per capita
health	Total health spending per capita. Given as %age of GDP per capita
imports	Imports of goods and services per capita. Given as %age of the GDP per capita
Income	Net income per person
Inflation	The measurement of the annual growth rate of the Total GDP
life_expec	The average number of years a new born child would live if the current mortality patterns are to remain the same
total_fer	The number of children that would be born to each woman if the current age-fertility rates remain the same.
gdpp	The GDP per capita. Calculated as the Total GDP divided by the total population.
